space-track.org 2011-09-29

# Space-Track - Website Privacy Statement

### Space-Track.Org Web Site Privacy Statement

**Web Site Privacy and Security Notices, Web Site Disclaimer, and Accessibility Statement**

Thank you for visiting this web site and reviewing its privacy and security notices.

**Web Site Privacy Notice**

Cookie technology may be used to enhance your experience while accessing this web site. At no time is private information you have provided – whether stored in cookies (persistent) or elsewhere – shared with third parties that have no right to that information. If you do not wish to have persistent cookies stored on your machine, you can turn them off in your browser. However, this may impact some of your functionality while visiting certain web sites.

Below are examples of what we do with your information when reading or downloading information from this Web site.

We may collect and store information for statistical purposes. For example, we may count the number of visitors to the different pages of our Web site to help make them more useful to visitors. This information does not identify you personally. We collect and store the following information about your visit automatically:

  * The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access the web site; 

  * The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;

  * The date and time you access our site;

  * The pages you visit; and

  * If you visited this web site from a link on another Web site, the address of that Web site.

Similar information is gathered for anonymous ftp, remote account login, or for other comparable types of connections.

The information that you provide to administrators of this web site will be used only for its intended purpose, except as required by law, or if pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings.

**When Sending Us E-Mail**

By sending us an electronic mail (e-mail) message, you may be sending us personal information such as your name, address, and e-mail address. We may store your name, address, and e-mail address of the requester in order to respond to your request or otherwise resolve the subject matter of the e-mail. Under certain limited circumstances, we may be required by law to disclose the information you submit.

Remember that e-mail is not necessarily secure against interception. If your communication is sensitive, or includes personal information such as your Social Security number, you should consider sending it by postal mail instead.

**When Registering**

Information collected through questionnaires, feedback forms, or other means, enables us to determine visitors' interests, with the goal of providing better service to our visitors.

Regardless of the information being transmitted, we will protect all such information consistent with the principles of the Federal Records Act, the Privacy Act, and as applicable, the Freedom of Information Act.

**Web Site Security**

For site security purposes and to ensure that this web-based service remains available to all users, this computer system employs software programs that monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Anyone using this system expressly consents to such monitoring and is advised that if such monitoring reveals evidence of possible abuse or criminal activity, such evidence may be provided to appropriate law enforcement officials. Unauthorized attempts to upload or change information are strictly prohibited and may be punishable by law, including the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act of 1996.

**© 2004 Space-Track.Org - All rights reserved.**
